I want to know your reaction when you
found out you're going where Quinn was,
but not only him, uh, Michael Taff and
Trey Moore drafted earlier in the same
day.
So, my immediate reaction was, um, it's
just time to run it back again. You
know, I had three years with Quinn and,
you know, he got drafted last year and
it was just like a reunion seeing Taff
and Treymore go right before me. And
then once I got that call, I was like,
it's time to go to work with my brothers
again.
And I understand in recent years, Sarkc
at at Texas that ran a lot of the same
concepts, maybe even some of the same
plays as the Dolphins. Uh, now that was
the Dolphins offense under Mike McDaniel
here. I think it'll be somewhat similar
with Bobby Sloick as as OC, but how much
can that familiarity uh help you in your
transition to the pros?
>> Um, I think it'll help me a lot just
because like you said, I'm familiar with
it and how to structure goals. So, I
think me getting in there and just
learning the playbook and just learning
how to contribute to the team would
would be easy, especially coming from
the same similar style offense.
>> Cool. Appreciate it. Thank you.
>> Thank you,
>> Chris.
>> Hey, DJ Chris Perkins, South Florida Sun
Sentinel. How you doing?
>> I'm doing great. How about you?
>> I'm good. I'm good. Uh, glad to see you
lived in Arlington. I went to UTA, lived
in Arlington for 10 years. So, yeah.
That's cool. That's cool. Hey, uh I'm
doing a couple of things here. Um one,
it's on um the draft night experience
for you and you know, sometimes guys
expect to go higher and they're upset.
Sometimes guys are grateful to have
their names called and it's a big party.
First of all, how was your draft night
experience?
>> So, my draft night, well, my three
nights experience was kind of a little
bit hectic, a little bit stressful just
because I didn't know what range I was
coming from. I was hearing a lot from
from anywhere from a chance of taking
from early second all the way from the
fifth and sixth round. So, it was just a
a wide range of where I could go. So, we
didn't really know exactly where I could
go. So, that was kind of just I say the
most stressful part about it, but I had
my family around me and some of my close
friends. I didn't really throw like a
big party. So, it wasn't I didn't have
that much pressure for sure.
>> And then the the other thing is whether
you feel as though you're an underdog
coming into the league. I mean, you've
been at the top of the food chain your
entire athletic career. Um, and and now
you're a a lower round NFL draft pick.
Do do you feel like you're the same big
dog you were at Texas or how do you feel
like you come in as an underdog here? Um
so as of right now I definitely feel
more more humbled about my experience
especially getting drafted in the sixth
round just because um it was something
that I never like really imagined myself
doing you know coming from high school
and then um transitioning to college I
always wanted to be like a first round
pick is um one of the reasons why I came
back this year or last year was to
really improve my draft stock. So I
don't feel like um you know I'm like
underrated or anything like that. I just
feel like I'm coming in with the right
chip on my shoulder and this is kind of
what I needed to really get that dog in
me for sure.
>> Yeah. Okay. Thanks, DJ. Congrats.
>> Appreciate that.
>> Isaiah, what's
>> going on? DJ Isaiah Smalls from the
Miami Herald. How are you?
>> Doing great. How about you?
>> Cool. I'm cool. Congratulations.
Uh my first question for you is you're
part of a draft class that seemingly
emphasized physicality um particularly
in the run game when it comes to the
offensive players selected. I'm curious,
what's your approach to run blocking?
>> Uh my approach to run blocking is really
just uh being physical and trying to
move my my man away from the play as
much as possible. Um especially learning
coming in now, learning different
technique and and how to attack the
block. Definitely just learning to apply
that this upcoming season and then just
really transition my game.
>> That's what's up. That's what's up. And
then final question for you. I asked
this to your, you know, former teammate,
so I'm curious what uh you say. Um, but
what did the Dolphins get in Michael and
Trey?
>> Uh, they got some real nice dogs and and
real big leaders. Um, Mike Michael and
Trey Moore did a great job of leading
the defense this year and last year. You
know, Trey Moore was on his fifth year
and so was Mike. So, they was already uh
pretty much veterans on the team and you
see how they played. They didn't. They
was relentless and the energy kept going
and that's how it was off the field as
well.
>> Cool. Appreciate you. Congrats again.
>> Thank you,
>> Travis.
>> Hey, what's up DJ? Congrats on being
drafted here by the Dolphins. Uh, I read
a quote from you where you said you
can't imagine yourself being happy doing
anything else but playing football. So,
I guess the question is, why is football
so important to you? Um, football is so
important to me just because it's it's a
sport that I can really release all my
inner feelings out on another, you know,
another man, you know, and just have fun
with it. That's really the main thing. I
like to win games and just experiencing
that that that moment with your brothers
that you worked hard for in the
offseason, the hard workouts all leading
up to that moment whenever you do win is
just a a feeling of relief whenever it
pays off.
>> So, you close your career with 43
consecutive starts. I know this is kind
of a lot to ask, but is there a moment
that stands out to you above the rest?
Whether it was a block you made, a drive
within a game, a game itself, is there a
moment to look back on and say that was
the best version of DJ Campbell at
Texas?
>> Um,
I definitely want to say these last
three years, not my freshman year, my
freshman year was kind of like a trying
to get used to it, trying to get
adjusted and trying to just really find
my my way on the team. But these last
three years has just been fun and um I
just been trying to bust heads every
game and every every play, every
opportunity I got, I was just trying to,
you know, exert myself.
>> Appreciate it, man. Thank you.
>> Thank you,
>> Joe.
>> Hey, DJ. It's Joe in Palm Beach. It's
nice to meet you. So, I just want to
make sure there's there's no periods in
DJ, right? It's just DJ. No periods.
>> Yes, sir. Just DJ. Have you ever asked
anyone uh why no periods or have you
ever thought about putting that in
there?
>> No, I haven't. I always just gone by
that. My first name is Devon. My middle
name is James. So, let's just go DJ.
>> Devon James. Got it.
>> Yeah. A lot of people mispronounce it.
They call me Devin. And it's just I
don't really like it.
>> Okay. Okay. Um
Trey Moore, can you give me a little
more of an onfield scouting report? What
do you think he does best on the
football field?
>> Um, he's shifty. Um, which like he's a
jack of all trades when it comes down to
lining up. When he was to walk down on
edge, he'll hit you with a hesy spin or
the next one he'll hit you with the full
spin. So, he'll kind of try to shake off
a little bit and then he got some
unexpected power. He got to him. So, he
will long arm you, he'll catch you off
guard with that one. It's just when it
comes to tres like basketball, him and
Colin Simmons was was really great at
doing that. It's like they playing
basketball on the field. It was them two
that you know you had to really come
with your agame when going to USM 101
ones especially like the pass rush for
sure.
>> Good stuff. Thank you DJ.
>> Thank you
>> Barry.
>> Hi DJ. That was a great scouting report
on Trey. Could you please share one with
Michael as well? What he did at safety
and the skills that could translate to
the NFL?
>> Yeah, like I said, Michael Michael he's
just relentless with it. His energy is
outstanding and he's a smart player. So
he's going to try to beat you to the
spot before you even get there. He's
going to try to call out the offense. He
see tight end in motion. He already knew
what's going on. Like you said, he was
he been there for a long time. So in
practice, he pretty much knew what was
going down. So you just had to really be
there to beat him. Really?
>> Thank you.
>> He was real smart and real swifty on the
field.